physioadvisor.com.au 2013-05-19

# PhysioAdvisor - Privacy Policy

|  | 

We at PhysioAdvisor.com, take the privacy of our visitors very seriously. Any personal information supplied to us will not be sold, passed on or disclosed to any third parties apart from our product suppliers (this is necessary for fulfillment of orders and will only occur when a product is purchased).

We will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or email address) through our Website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us.

Information that is supplied to us voluntarily may be used to provide personalised features and services, to analyse the use of the site and provide better information to our site visitors.

Email addresses obtained voluntarily through the use of PhysioAdvisor will be used to send email updates periodically about any changes or updates to the site. We may also send email messages to you containing advertisements or promotions from time to time. We will NOT sell, rent, pass on or disclose these lists to any third party. You can unsubscribe from this list at any time.

Cookies may be used by us to enhance user experience and provide easy access through the site. If you wish to turn off cookies, this can be done within your browser by going to 'Tools / Internet Options / Privacy' and selecting to block cookies. Or alternatively, refer to your browser instructions for further information about these functions. By choosing to turn off cookies, you may be unable to use certain features of PhysioAdvisor.com. The use of cookies does not involve the collection of any personal data.

We may use general traffic, site usage and length-of-stay information in reports to advertisers and firms with which we have a business relationship. This information does not personally identify you.

We may also collect technical information when you connect to our site including: the type of computer operating system you are using, the internet browser you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site.

Our website may contain links to other internet websites. Please be aware that when you click on one of these links, you are leaving our website and entering another. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to read their privacy policy statement.

We use third-party advertising companies (including Google) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. This may occur at any time, without notice. 

|   
---|---|---
